{"data":[{"question":"The hurricane, coming while it did, took the Florida coastal community by surprise.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"coming ","b":"while ","c":"took ","d":"by surprise","answer":"2","explain":"- While-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Scientists have recently argued that Einstein's contribution to physics and  mathematics are less important as Newton's.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have recently argued ","b":"to ","c":"are less ","d":"as ","answer":"3","explain":"- are less-> is as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Even the most discriminating gourmet will agree that food in the South is as good as any other region in the country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"discriminating","b":"that ","c":"good ","d":"as any other ","answer":"4","explain":"- as any other-> as in any other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The study of astronomy is so recent as the past centuries, but astrology has existed for thousands of years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"so ","b":"but ","c":"astrology ","d":"has existed for ","answer":"1","explain":"- So-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Microwave oven thermometers are more cost than other kinds of thermometers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are ","b":"cost ","c":"other ","d":"kinds ","answer":"2","explain":"- Cost->expensive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Mercury is the most small planet in the solar system and the closest to the sun.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Mercury ","b":"most small ","c":"in ","d":"closest to ","answer":"2","explain":"- Most small-> the smallest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"A painter who lived most of his life in the Middle West, Grant Wood has called America's Painter of the Soil.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A painter ","b":"most ","c":"his life ","d":"has called ","answer":"4","explain":"- Has called-> has been called","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Chromosomes as appear long, tangled threads when they first become visible during the  early prophase stage of mitosis.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"as appear ","b":"threads ","c":"first become ","d":"during ","answer":"1","explain":"- As appear-> appeared","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"In the Middle Ages, books called bestiaries were prepared in an attempt to describe animals, real or imagine, that exemplified human  traits.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"called ","b":"an attempt ","c":"real or imagine","d":"that ","answer":"3","explain":"- Real-> reality","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The relationship of Latin American music to Black music in the United States is clearly evident in the unaccented beats that are common to either.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of ","b":"to ","c":"clearly evident ","d":"either","answer":"4","explain":"- Either-> other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}